video-player-download.com 2018-06-06

# Video Media Player - Privacy Policy

The site carries only a statistical collection on the uses of users (where the user logs in, the browser used, operating system, etc. through the network Google Analytics) as shown in the cookie policy without any prompt for sensitive data such as name , Last Name, Address, Email etc.  
This site, through affiliate networks and advertising networks, provides the user with promotional offers, advertising and other services as described in this document.

**Update MAY 2018** \- “We may use [third-party advertising companies](http://d3r1ngl87mq5px.cloudfront.net/pp.html) to serve ads when you visit our website”.

### Website Owner

Advwebstudio 2.0 Srl - Via Fuardo, 10 - 94015 Piazza Armerina,

### Types of data collected

Use of Cookies - or other tracking tools - by this application or the owners of third party services used by this application, unless otherwise specified, aims to identify the User and register their preferences for purposes strictly tied to the provision of the service you request. The user assumes the responsibility of the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through this application and warrant that you have the right to communicate or disseminate them, freeing the owner from any liability to third parties.

### Place and methods of treatment of the data collected

## Treatment modalities

The owner of the site in the processing of Personal Data of the Users taking all necessary security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Personal Information.  
The treatment is carried out using computers and / or computer, with organizational methods and logic strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the owner, in some cases, they may have access to the data categories of personnel involved in the Site (administrative, commercial, marketing, legal, system administrators) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, responsible for processing by the Owner. The updated list of Managers can be requested from the Data Controller.

## Place

The data are processed at the operational headquarters of the Data Controller and in any other place where the parties involved in the treatment are located. For more information, contact the owner.

## Duration

The Data are kept for the time necessary to perform the service requested by you, or required by the objectives described in this document, and the User can always ask for discontinuation of treatment or deletion of data.

## The use of the data collected

The User Data is collected to allow the Owner to provide their services, as well as for the following purposes: Interaction with external social networks and platforms and Statistics.

The types of Personal Data used for each purpose are given in the specific sections of this document.

## Details concerning the processing of Personal Information

The Personal Data are collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

  * ## **Interaction with social networks, external platforms, outdoor advertising platforms**

  * These services allow you to make interactions with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Application. Interactions and the information gained from this application are in any case subject to the User's privacy settings related to each social network. If an installed service interaction with social networks, it is possible that, even if the users do not use the service, the same collect traffic data about the pages in which it is installed.

## Like button and social widgets for Facebook (Facebook, Inc.)

The "Like" Facebook and social widgets are services of interaction with the social network Facebook, provided by Facebook, Inc.

Personal data collected: Cookie and data usage.

Processing location: USA (for more information please read the privacy policy of Facebook named below) – [Privacy Policy](http://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php)

## **Tweet button and social widgets to Twitter (Twitter, Inc.)**

The Tweet button and social widgets are services of Twitter to interact with the social network Twitter, provided by Twitter, Inc.

Personal data collected: Cookie and data usage.

Processing location: USA (for more information please read the privacy policy of Twitter named below) – [Privacy Policy](http://twitter.com/privacy)

## **Google+ button and social widgets Google (Google Inc.)**

Google+ button and social widgets are Google services interaction with the social network Google+, provided by Google, Inc.

Personal data collected: Cookie and data usage.

Processing location: USA (for more information please read the privacy policy of Google named below) – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

**In this site Social buttons and / or Third party plugins are disabled (thus its profiling cookies are disabled) to accept cookies from the user.**

##  **Google Adsense advertising platform**

Sponsored ads, sponsored links and any form of advertising text or graphics are services by Google Adsense, provided by Google, Inc.

Personal data collected: Cookie and data usage.

Processing location: USA (for more information please read the privacy policy of Google named below) – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

**In this site Adsense ads and third-party advertisers are disabled (thus its profiling cookies are disabled) to accept cookies from the user.**

  * ## Statistics

The services contained in this section are used to the Owner to monitor and analyze traffic data and are used to keep track of User behavior.

Google Analytics (Google Inc.)

Google Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google uses Personal Information collected for the purpose of evaluating the use of this application, compile reports and share them with other services developed by Google.  
Google may use this personal information to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal data collected: Cookie and data usage.

Place of treatment: USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/it/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=it)

**In this website we use "Google Analytics anonymous" ie Analytics cookies are cookies "technical" by the use of "Google Analytics cookies with IP anonymized".**

### Further information on data processing

## **Courting**

The User's Personal Data may be used for the defense by the Owner in court or in the stages leading to possible legal action, against improper use of the same or related services by the User.  
The User declares to be aware that the owner may be required to disclose the information requested by the public authorities.

## **Specific information**

At your request, in addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this could provide the User Application of additional and contextual information about specific services, or the collection and processing of Personal Information.

## **System logs and maintenance**

For needs related to operation and maintenance, this Application and any third party services it uses may collect system logs, which are files that record the interactions and may also contain Personal Information, such as IP address User.

## **Information not contained in this policy**

Further information in relation to the processing of Personal Information may be requested at any time to the Owner using the contact information.

## **Exercise of rights by Users**

Those whose Personal Data refer have the right at any time to obtain confirmation of the existence of the same at the Data Controller, to know the content and origin, to check its accuracy or request its integration , deleting, updating, rectification, erasure, anonymisation or blocking of Personal Data processed in violation of law, and to oppose in any case, for legitimate reasons, to their treatment. Requests should be addressed to the Owner.

This application does not support requests "Do Not Track". To know whether any third-party services used to support, see their privacy policy.

## **Changes to this privacy policy**

The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving publicity to the Users on this page. Please therefore check this page often, by reference to the date of last modification indicated at the bottom. In case of rejection of the changes made to this privacy policy, the user is required to end the use of this application and can take to the Owner to remove their Personal Data. Unless otherwise specified, the previous privacy policy will continue to apply to personal information collected until then.

## **Information about this privacy policy**

The Data Processing of the data is responsible for this privacy policy, drafted from the modules provided by Iubenda and stored on its servers.

### Legal references and definitions

## Personal Information (or data)

It constitutes personal data any information relating to an individual, identified or identifiable, even indirectly, by reference to any other information including a personal identification number.

## Data of Use

Is the information collected automatically by this application (or by third-party applications that use this application), including: IP addresses or domain names of the computers used by the users who connect with this application, addresses in URI (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of request, the method used to submit the request to the server, the file size obtained in response, the numerical code indicating the status of response from the server (successful, error, etc. ) the country of origin, the features of the browser and operating system used by the visitor, the various time details per visit (for instance the time spent on each page) and the details about the path followed within the Application, with particular reference to the sequence of pages visited, the parameters related to the operating system and computer environment.

## User

The individual who uses this application, which must coincide with the involved or be approved by that State and whose Personal Data are being processed.

## Personal Data Subject

The natural or legal person to whom the Personal Data.

## Data Processor (or Manager)

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization designated by the Owner to the processing of Personal Data, as prepared by this privacy policy.

## Data Controller (or owner)

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other organization, association or organization that is competent, also jointly with another data, decisions regarding the purposes, methods of processing of personal data and the tools used, including the profile of Safety in connection with the operation and use of this application. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the owner of this application.

## This Application

The instrument hardware or software by which collected the Personal Information Users.

## Cookie

Small piece of data stored within the device user.

* * *

### Legal information

Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of the Directive n. 95/46 / EC and with the provisions of Directive 2002/58 / EC, as updated by Directive 2009/136 / EC, with regard to Cookies.

This privacy policy applies only this application.
